oyaop.com 2019-06-18

# Privacy Policy - OYA Opportunities

## Who we are

OYA Opportunities is a subsidiary of OYA INC. It is a global platform for the youth where youth are exposed to opportunities to fill the colours in your dreams. It is a connecting link between youth and various sectors full of opportunities. Our website address is: [https://oyaop.com](https://oyaop.com/).

At OYA Opportunities, accessible from oyaop.com, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by OYA Opportunities and how we use it.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Contact forms

When you contact us via contact form on the site we collect the data shown in the contact form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Google DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google is one of a third-party vendor on our site. It also uses cookies, known as DART cookies, to serve ads to our site visitors based upon their visit to www.website.com and other sites on the internet. However, visitors may choose to decline the use of DART cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network Privacy Policy at the following URL – <https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads>

### Our Advertising Partners

Some of advertisers on our site may use cookies and web beacons. Our advertising partners are listed below. Each of our advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their policies on user data. For easier access, we hyperlinked to their Privacy Policies below.

  * Google<https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads>

#### Privacy Policies

You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of OYA Opportunities.

  * https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites

Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on OYA Opportunities, which are sent directly to users’ browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.

Note that OYA Opportunities has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

#### Third Pary Privacy Policies

OYA Opportunities’s Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. You may find a complete list of these Privacy Policies and their links here: Privacy Policy Links.

You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. [What Are Cookies?](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/cookies-information-websites-store-on-your-computer)

### Children’s Information

Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.

OYA Opportunities does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Log Files

OYA Opportunities follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services’ analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.

Furthermore, OYA Opportunities also uses third-party analytics tools such as Google Analytics and WordPress.com analytics by Automattic. Each of our analytics providers has their own Privacy Policy for their policies on user data.

## Who we share your data with

OYA Opportunities does not sell or rent personal information to third parties. OYA Opportunities will not disclose your personal information to a third party without your permission, except in connection with performing your background screen for OYA Opportunities’s client or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.

OYA Opportunities may disclose personal information as necessary or appropriate in connection with any of the purposes for which we use personal information as described above in “What personal data we collect and why we collect it”.

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in OYA Opportunities. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

## Contact information

If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us through email at contact@oyaop.com.
